[{"answer": "This place looks great with the all the trees and good road", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Maybe the campsite will have some privacy with thick bushes and trees. Let", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 16, "question": "This place looks great with the all the trees and good road", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Well drive through the park first, to see what spots are available", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Maybe the campsite will have some privacy with thick bushes and trees. Let", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " That spot looks goodplenty of room for the tent", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Well drive through the park first, to see what spots are available", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Lets keep looking", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 22, "question": " That spot looks goodplenty of room for the tent", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Hey, heres a spot, and the restroom and showers are very close by", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Lets keep looking", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": "Youre right", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Hey, heres a spot, and the restroom and showers are very close by", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Mommy, Im hungry", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 25, "question": "Youre right", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " OK, sweetie, when we pull into the campsite in a couple minutes, well open th", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Mommy, Im hungry", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Yes, that spot near the showers is the best spot", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 33, "question": " OK, sweetie, when we pull into the campsite in a couple minutes, well open th", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Great. Here we are. Lets unpack the cooler, and make some sandwiches o", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Yes, that spot near the showers is the best spot", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " OK, Mommy, let me help", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Great. Here we are. Lets unpack the cooler, and make some sandwiches o", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " I think I will have lunch before I set up the tent", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 39, "question": " OK, Mommy, let me help", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " This is lots of work, Daddy", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 40, "question": " I think I will have lunch before I set up the tent", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Yeah, but its fun.  Were going to be outside the whole time we are on vacation", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 41, "question": " This is lots of work, Daddy", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Yeah, and we can sleep in the tent and hear all the night sounds", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Yeah, but its fun.  Were going to be outside the whole time we are on vacation", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": "Look, theres a squirrel thats come to see us. Maybe well see some bunnies o", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Yeah, and we can sleep in the tent and hear all the night sounds", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Yeah, maybe we can leave some bread crumbs for the bunnies", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Look, theres a squirrel thats come to see us. Maybe well see some bunnies o", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Well, bunnies usually like carrots.  The birds might like the bread crumbs. I sa", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Yeah, maybe we can leave some bread crumbs for the bunnies", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " And you know, I saw a hiking trail close to the entrance.  Maybe tomorrow w", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Well, bunnies usually like carrots.  The birds might like the bread crumbs. I sa", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Maybe we can go fishing in the lake", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 60, "question": " And you know, I saw a hiking trail close to the entrance.  Maybe tomorrow w", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Yes, Daddys a good fisherman, you know", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Maybe we can go fishing in the lake", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Lets set up the tent. Where is the duffel bag", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Yes, Daddys a good fisherman, you know", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " I took it out of the truck and put it under the picnic table, next to the sleepin", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Lets set up the tent. Where is the duffel bag", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " OK, where are the stakes", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 67, "question": " I took it out of the truck and put it under the picnic table, next to the sleepin", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Theyre in the other bag", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 68, "question": " OK, where are the stakes", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " There are only five stakes.  Were missing one. Uh oh.  What will we us", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Theyre in the other bag", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Well, there are plenty of rocks around here.  We could use a couple of them t", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 75, "question": " There are only five stakes.  Were missing one. Uh oh.  What will we us", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Good idea.  Thats what happens when you go camping", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Well, there are plenty of rocks around here.  We could use a couple of them t", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Yes.  Let nature work for you", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Good idea.  Thats what happens when you go camping", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " I am hot from finding rocks, so Im going to take a cold shower now", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Yes.  Let nature work for you", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " OK, sweetie, dont forget to take your towel and soap with you", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 82, "question": " I am hot from finding rocks, so Im going to take a cold shower now", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Glad you remembered the soap, Mom", "docId": "09-10", "aSentId": 83, "question": " OK, sweetie, dont forget to take your towel and soap with you", "qSentId": 82}]
